Hello Hello Friends Welcome to our YouTube
channel Info Gyan Friends In today's video we will
share some banking updates with you. In
this update ICICI Bank has made a
new announcement for its customers. The
bank is constantly making changes to its system
so that customers do
not have to face any kind of problem.
Today a new service has been launched in the bank
which hardly anyone else is offering till now.
Through this service, you will be able to do banking transactions without touching the phone,
just by speaking. The
bank has integrated its AEG powered multichannel
Chapter Note IPL with two of the world's
popular voice assistant apps Amazon
Electra and Google Assistant to
simplify the banking process for its retail banking customers. This facility has been
started because
due to the Ombudsman, people are not able to go to the bank branch, that is
why they have to use the bank's app.
Next update Paytm
Payments
Limited said that it has crossed the deposit mark of
Rs 100 crore with 5711 savings bank accounts.
BAIL says
that this increase is due to configuration.  This has happened due to the increasing adoption of
digital banking. The
bank has now also started the Direct Benefit Transfer
facility, through which
funds transferred by the Government of India can also be
transferred to their accounts. Benefits of all social
welfare scheme subsidies, LPG gas
subsidy, old age pension, MNREGA payment,
scholarships, etc. can be
availed in these accounts.
Next Update: Kotak Mahindra Bank has reduced the
savings deposit interest rate for the second time this month. The
bank had
reduced the interest rate from April 1,
after which the interest rate has been reduced again from April 20. The
bank has reduced the interest rate
for customers having deposits of less than Rs 1 lakh in its savings account to
3.75 percent and
4.5 percent for deposits above Rs 1 lakh.
Next Update:
After the relief given in loan moratorium, RBI has now announced that
penal interest will not be charged on crop loans given to farm applicants.
Earlier, the
actress had also extended the moratorium on installments.  The loan was
given for the period from
March 1st to May 31st. However,
interest will be charged on the loan. Now,
in the latest announcement, it has been said that no
penal interest will be charged from the farmers
and the benefit of interest subsidy will also remain. The
government has also continued the benefit
of 3% subsidy given to the farmers
if the
repayment date of the farmer's loan is during this period
so that the farmer does
not have to go to the bank due to the Ignorance Ombudsman. Next update: HDFC
Limited has given relief to home loan customers. The
company has reduced its loan interest
rate by 0.25% on Tuesday. At present,
borrowing costs in the system are continuously falling.
In a statement, the company said that
HDFC has reduced its
retail prime lending rate for housing loans
to 0.15%. This rate is the benchmark rate for the company's affordable
rate home loans. The
lending rates will be
effective from April 22, 2010. This reduction will
benefit all existing retail home loan customers of HDFC.  The new interest rates will now be
between 7.85% and 8.15% annually.
Friends, these were some banking updates.
For all such banking updates,
subscribe to our channel.
Like and share the video. Thank you, all the best.